VALENTINA MARENDA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

valentinamarenda1@gmail.com

+ 54 (0221) 15-5716173

• La Plata - Buenos Aires - Argentina

10/18/1990

in /valentinamarenda

/valenmarenda

www.valenmarenda.com.ar

SKILLS WEB DEVELOPMENT

5 HTML

Js JavaScript

3 CSS

San SASS

MySQL

◆ GIT

Php PHP

GITHUB node Node JS

Mongo DB 🔑 Firebase

LANGUAGE

Level: C1 - Advanced

ABOUT ME

I am currently a web developer specializing in React js. I studied full stack web development at Coder House, which allowed me to start my career and work on many development projects.

My goal is to be part of a company that will allow me to continue to grow professionally as a programmer.

EDUCATION

- Full Stack Development: includes the courses:
- React Js
- JavaScript
- Web development
- Backend development

Coderhouse 2020

• Course: Microfrontends: a complete guide.

Udemy 2022

• Course: Web development HTML5, CSS3, JS AJAX PHP y MySQL.

Udemy 2020 - Finished

• Course: Social media management & digital marketing

Start digital School 2019 - Finished

Course: Coaching & leadership

FCA 2019 - Finished

· Course: Academic english

(8 months in Dublin, Irlanda) - Chapter House Irlanda - Finished

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer 2021 - present

Contabilium

- Application development with microfrontend design, React is and Node is

Frontend Developer 2021

Wualá

- Ecommerce website development

Full stack developer freelance 2021 - present

Website development for institutions and companies Websites updating

React JS tutor 2021 - present

Coder House

- Checking and assessing student work
- Planning, preparing and delivering after class lessons

Mentor 2021 - 2022

Nucba

- Checking and assessing student work
- Planning, preparing and delivering class lessons

Marketing and sales manager 2019 - 2021

Hotel - Head of marketing and Sales

Marketing and sales manager 2014 - 2019

Este University

Head of Marketing and publicity